ABDISALAN AWALE

37 Mill Park Drive, Mill Park 3082 Mobile: 0416649127

Email: awaleaseir@gmail.com

Objectives

An energetic, open-minded and self-motivated committed outreach customer service consultant, with eight years of experience in a range of customer service and data entry roles. A quick learner who uses humour and integrity to build trust in any given setting.

Education

- Completed year 12 VCE at Kownain Secondary College-2007
- **PSA** Certificate ii- 2011
- Bachelor of Information Management Systems-2012

Employment History

♦ Uber- 2015 - Current

Responsibilities

- Customer Service
- Communication skills
- Time Management

•

♦ Motor spirit L.M.C.T - Dec 2016 - 2017

Responsibilities

- Customer service
- Data Entry
- Preparing Spreadsheets
- Maintaining customer relationships

HIMILO Enterprise, Melbourne - Feb 2012 - Nov 2016

Responsibilities

- Minimizing customer debts by negotiating maximum repayment arrangements with the customer or their representative.
- Sending remittances.
- Educating customers on the products and services.
- Maintaining customer relationships.
- Using sophisticated technology to improve the collections operations business.
- Strive to exceed departmental targets and service levels.
- Data entry

Skills

- Strong computer skills
- Web-development- html-css-javascript
- Ability to build relationships with people from a broad spectrum of backgrounds
- Demonstrated conflict management and consultation skills as group leader at university group assignments.
- Demonstrated ability to motivate, influence, supervise and coordinate group processes through development of agendas, minutes, group rules and group project timelines (gained through group research assignments).
- Demonstrated ability to work independently and under pressure

Personal Interests

- Programming
- Reading
- Travelling
- Cycling

References

Himilo Enterprise

Duty manager

Zaem: 0401968493

Motor spirit

Manager

Khadija: 0431816344